Oh, for God's sake.
Planking is a very stupid
and dangerous trend.
Basically you lie like
a plank in weird places.
That's it.
Sometimes you get run over.
Welcome to the Internet.
Planking is one of
those things where,
hey, you either
get it or you don't.
And I don't.
But I am so excited
to be a part of it.
After you,
my good sir.
No, I insist.
JIM:
The search committee
finally decided,
after a lot of deliberation,
on Robert California
for the manager position.
(COUGHING)
Who took one look
around and left.
He drove down to Florida
and convinced Jo
to make him C.E.O.
C.E.O. Her own job.
He talked her
out of her own job
and I don't really know
how someone does that,
but anyway,
then the position
was his to fill,
and he chose...
(FINGERS DRUMMING)
It's unbelievable.
ANDY: True. I may have
been the second choice,
but I was
the first choice's
first choice.
And about Dwight,
I sense that he might
have some resentment
about not getting the job,
so I sat him down
and we had a talk.
And I told him,
"I need a really
strong number two.
"I want you to
be my enforcer."
Smart, right?
Very smart.
This has got to stop.
I can't get down.
Hey! Kevin!
Yeah, at first I was
really disappointed.
But I've got a great
daily routine going
right now.
I've upped my karate
to eight times a week.
I've added boxing
at lunches
and on weekends,
I do kick-boxing
three times a week,
Krav Maga four times a week,
an hour of meditation
every morning at sunrise,
and again at sunset.
So yeah.
I'm doing great.
I'm going to need
some help. Pam?
I don't think I should.
Oh, yeah. Pregnant.
Right here.
Little Michael Scott.
Nope. I told you I
don't like that joke.
It is a boy.
We found out early.
Much different
the second time around.
And I have to say
it is nice not being
the only pregnant
woman in the office.
Look, it's
"little pregs" and
"big pregs."
Wait, when did we
start calling
each other...
Isn't it amazing
the difference in
our sizes?
Well, I am a few
months ahead of you.
I'm having
a child with my husband,
the senator.
And Pam
is having a child with Jim.
The great salesman.
Hoist him aloft!
Come on, Darryl, lift.
Lift, Darryl.
Come on, man.
Yeah, I wanted
the manager job, but I got
something much better.
This soda.
This is mine.
It might be easier if
you take a deep breath,
lift from the knees,
and shove it
up your butt.
(LAUGHING)
(KEVIN GROANS)
I came up with
a new thing this summer.
I act like I'm
telling someone how to
do something.
I go on with
a long description
and then I say...
And shove it up your butt.
(LAUGHING)
It's stupid,
but it's my thing now.
No one should be
planking at all.
Thank you. Yes.
Dwight,
my enforcer, my number two,
can you take care of this?
Say no more.
(THUDDING)
(MEREDITH YELPS)
Kids, don't try planking,
it's dangerous.
Especially with me around.
(SOULFUL SONG PLAYING)
(SNIFFLING)
Are you watching
that commercial again?
Why do you keep watching it
if you know it's just
going to make you cry?
Because
everything makes me cry,
so what's the difference?
This dog,
he just wants to
protect his bone.
He's got a bank vault.
That's a start.
Not enough, though.
All right.
(DOOR OPENING)
The new C.E.O. works out
of the conference room
about half the time,
but whenever he takes a break,
he does these weird
walks around the office.
And you never know
who he's going to
zero in on
for these really
intense small talks.
You just hope
it's not you.
And yet you
hope it is you, too.
It's strange.
Here we go.
Hello.
Robert California.
Let's have a conversation.
Describe your day so far.
Well, I woke up and...
When you recount
your day, never say
you woke up.
It's a waste of your time.
That's how every day
has begun for everyone
since the dawn of man.
Very smart.
Suddenly, I was awake
and I...
Hey, Robert.
We have that 9:30 A.M.
casual chit chat scheduled.
I emailed you about it
last night to confirm.
And again this morning.
First item on the agenda,
can I get everyone
an extra long
Columbus Day weekend?
Item number two,
connect with the guy.
Robert California,
what does he think of me?
Don't know.
Super care.
Number three, time permitting,
we lost our biggest client.
(WHISPERING)
Pam. Pam.
Psst! Pam.
(WHISPERS) Jim.
Can I call you right back?
Thank you very much.
Okay.
What is this?
The Friday before
Columbus Day, thoughts?
What are your thoughts?
Just making chit-chat.
Kind of a medium year
for women's soccer, no?
(WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
What are you looking at?
It's nothing.
It can't be nothing.
Yeah, it can't be nothing.
It's just
a list of our names
split into two columns.
What?
Okay, just wait one second,
all right?
I will copy it.
Do you have a pen?
No.
Okay. Um, I'll take
a photo of it.
Dwight, can you
throw me my phone?
Nice catch.
If he comes out,
distract him.
We need a warning signal.
We don't need
a warning signal, Kevin.
We can see him
right there.
KEVIN: We do.
I promise you we
don't need a...
Warning! Warning!
Warning!
JIM: Phyllis!
Phyllis!
DWIGHT: You okay?
(GROANING)
Yeah. Yeah.
DWIGHT: (GRUNTS)
One, two, three.
PHYLLIS: Thanks, guys.
Okay. Which side
of the list am I on?
Left.
Yes!
Why are you...
How do you know?
Really great
list of names, guys.
Thank you so much.
Good work.
No, actually, that was
in Robert's notebook.
He left it at reception
and we photocopied it.
Oh!
Okay. I don't want
any part of this.
Maybe it's the list of people
he's going to fire.
Okay.
It's not that, Pam.
You know,
I was thinking it
reminds me
of those lists
Dwight used to make.
This is if we were all
on a cruise ship
and had to divide
into life boats.
And this is if we
were on a cruise ship
and had to divide
into life rafts.
Here's something.
"Who would eat who
in an Alive situation?"
No. That can't be it.
ANDY: I gotta say,
it kind of seems
like the left side
is the side to be on.
Me, Jim, Dwight, Darryl,
no offense, Pam.
I don't think...
Excuse me?
Shh. Pam, come on.
Don't be
such a right-sider.
Did you guys
figure it out?
We couldn't crack it.
Go in there, just ask
the man what it means.
He'll know that we looked
at his private notebook.
Come on.
Just say you saw
the list by accident.
I'm already working
on this Columbus Day
thing for you guys.
And it's starting
to stack up.
It feels like a lot.
One thing at a time.
Yeah, that's all
you had to do today is
ask about Columbus Day?
Yes. For God's sake,
Andy, yes. Come in.
What's up?
Weird thing.
Totally awkward.
But you left your notebook
on the reception desk.
Great. Thank you.
And it was open,
and people saw this,
and they're just
kind of going nuts
and, like...
What is this?
...wondering what it is.
It's a photocopy
from your notebook.
You read my notebook?
And photocopied it
and distributed it?
(LAUGHS)
No. They did.
And they asked me
to ask you about it.
(GROANS)
Please.
Oh.
Here's what it is,
it's a doodle.
What?
Some people doodle at work
when they let their mind run.
They draw houses, penises,
funny how the houses
are always colonials
and the penises are
always circumcised.
Don't you think?
Well, I doodle too
but I'm not an artist
so I draw words and lists.
That is fascinating.
And by the way,
I am so glad I asked.
People were just sort of...
Did you just move my name?
Might as well have
been sketching a cube.
Okay, Robert's in the annex,
everybody think quick.
What do these
groups have in common?
Maybe we're supposed to
do it with people
in our group.
That's not it.
People in
the other group.
Mmm. Still wrong.
Stanley,
you do puzzles all day.
What do we got?
Well, you take
the first letter
from each name,
assign it a number,
add them all up,
and shove it up your butt.
(LAUGHS)
Thank you, a little
much needed comic relief.
But we really need to
figure this out, guys.
I know.
It's alphabetical.
(ALL DISAGREEING)
ANDY: No, it's not.
Here's how we find out.
Let's line up and
compare the lines,
see if we learn
anything, okay?
Left-siders over here,
right-siders
line up over here,
face each other.
Match up by height
and relative weight.
Let's just size
each other up here.
And left side of the list,
attack!
Wait, wait, wait,
stop, stop!
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
JIM: Will you stop?
Dwight!
Don't do it!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Warning! Warning! Warning!
I'd like to invite
the following people
to join me for lunch.
Jim, Dwight,
Angela, Darryl,
Kevin, Toby,
Phyllis, Oscar.
That's great.
Let's do this, guys.
All right. Well,
I will see you in a bit.
I love you so much.
Hey, it's nothing,
all right?
I'll text you
when we get there.
I'll let you know
what's going on.
Okay.
No. No dog video.
See you, guys.
Well, we should all
be really excited about
our very own pizza party.
Pizza party!
Pizza party.
Jim, your daughter Cecelia,
what does she
think of the Street?
The street?
Sesame Street.
Oh. I didn't know
anybody called it...
She likes it a lot.
She loves Elmo.
Elmo,
God save us,
the Elmo era.
Right?
Sesame Street was
created to reflect
the environment of
the children watching it.
Complete self
absorption of Elmo
is brilliantly
reflective of our time.
Ours is a cultural ghetto.
Wouldn't you agree?
Yeah. She does like Elmo.
Cultural ghetto?
Totally agree.
Completely.
Apt. Apt analysis, Robert.
The thing that I
like about Elmo
is the tickling.
I should not be here.
I don't know.
I was in the wrong...
I'm... I'm sorry.
Just picture me
back there.
I was never here.
Great group.
Pizza party.
How is this a pizza party?
Well, why don't you
ask me again
when the five pizzas
get here?
Yeah, well,
that's just pizza.
You need at least
one other element
for it to be a party.
Okay. Have you guys
ever had margherita pizza?
What's that?
Fresh tomato with a dollop
of mozzarella cheese.
That's pizza.
That's regular pizza.
You know, I feel
comfortable enough now
to ask you this question,
what made you
pick this group?
I just think
you guys are winners
and I wanted to
have lunch with you.
Okay.
Aw.
What about the other guys?
Losers? Come on.
Oh, I don't know.
Come on. Come on.
I guess I think
they're losers.
(LAUGHS) I knew it.
Yes!
Probably shouldn't
have said that.
DWIGHT: Whoo-hoo!
Ah-ha!
Their interpretation
of margherita pizza.
Fans of classic pizza
will be psyched.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
A text from Jim.
"This is getting very weird.
Will explain later."
(CELL PHONES CHIMING)
Text from Kevin.
"Suck it, losers."
RYAN:
Okay, not to point out
the glaringly obvious,
but doesn't the fact
that I'm in this group
make anyone feel just
a little bit better?
Oh, this crust is sharp!
I used to be young and cute
and sort of funny
and I could do those
cute little cartoons
and everyone who
came through here
was like,
"Who's that receptionist?
I like her."
Now I'm just a fat mom.
Yeah,
and you take one look at me
and you're like, "Oh, loser."
ANDY: Come here, Pam.
Chins up, okay?
(SNORTS) Bad joke.
Look around this room.
Does this look like
a group of losers?
Seriously.
Oh, God.
KELLY: Oh, hey, guys,
we had so much fun.
We had margherita pizza.
We all hung out
and got to know
each other better.
How was your lunch?
It was excellent.
Good times.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, we did.
It was the best time.
And you know what?
Now it's over,
back to work, everyone.
You too, Andy.
KEVIN: I knew it.
I just knew my whole life
that everyone
was wrong about me.
My parents,
my teachers, my friends,
the doctors, everyone.
Well, that was
certainly an odd lunch.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just take the
casserole out of the...
Loser.
Take it out of
the refrigerator,
put it in the oven.
It'll be fine.
Just leave it in
for 20 minutes.
KEVIN: Loser.
When I was a salesman,
I could just be like,
"Not my job, not my prob.
I'm going to the warehouse
to polish my knob."
Metaphorically, of course.
But now,
it is my job and my prob.
Hi, Robert.
Can you
come out here, please?
It's really important.
I just wanted to
clarify something.
Some people here
are under the misconception
that some people
may be considered,
let's say top tier,
and others would
be second tier.
I never said that.
Thank you. Great.
I said winners and losers.
Is that what
you're talking about?
Oh, that might...
That actually might be
what I'm thinking of.
Can you clarify that?
Let me tell you some
things I find productive.
Positive reinforcement,
negative reinforcement.
Honesty.
I'll tell you some things
I find unproductive.
Constantly worrying
about where you stand
based on
inscrutable social clues,
and then
inevitably reframing it all
in a reassuring way
so that you can get
to sleep at night.
No, I do not
believe in that at all.
If I invited you to lunch,
I think you're a winner.
If I didn't, I don't.
But I just met you all.
Life is long,
opinions change.
Winners, prove me right.
Losers, prove me wrong.
Well, I guess
that's that.
No.
No. No.
Andy, don't go in there.
I'm going in there.
I know that
every time I talk to you
things just seem to get worse.
But you don't know
these people, and I do.
And if I let you work
with faulty information,
well,
then I'm not doing my job
as regional manager.
So, please take this pen
and change your list.
I'm not going to
change my list, Andy.
And I don't use
ballpoint pens.
Well, then I will
make a new list for you.
Stanley, you may think
he's a lazy grump,
but did you know that
he has the most consistently
high sales numbers
of anyone in this office?
And you may think
he's hard to love,
but did you know
that he's in not one,
but two long-term
romantic relationships?
I did not know
about the sales figures.
Meredith Palmer,
supplier relations.
The word "no,"
not even in her vocabulary.
And just to show you
that I'm being fair,
you had Gabe in
the loser column,
I think that is astute.
Good call.
Pam,
easily the most
creative and kind person
I have ever worked with.
Jim, shut the door.
This is just gross.
Shh.
Erin Hannon, the receptionist,
and my closest confidant.
A winner if
there ever was one.
I like my new group.
I liked my old group.
Are we done?
Yes.
No.
The Friday
before Columbus Day,
we're going to
take a half-day.
So that
everyone can get a jump
on the long weekend.
You want
a three-and-a-half day
weekend for Columbus Day?
Yes, I do.
And you are aware that
Columbus and his legions
committed genocide against
an entire civilization
of Native Americans?
I don't care.
Hey, guys,
so Columbus Day,
we got that
half-day on Friday.
We get that every year.
Well, you got it
this year, too.
Good night, Andy.
Good night.
Bye.
Good night, Andy.
Good night.
Night.
All right, I'm going
to go warm up the car.
Okay.
You dropped something. Jim?
Okay, I know
I've been crying easily
today, but...
I mean, that's just
pretty killer, right?
I mean,
maybe it's stupid.
No.
It's wonderful.
I'm going to frame it.
I can always un-frame it.